{"questions":[[{"question":"what is agile methodology?\u2019","level":"difficult","answers":["designing method","an iterative approach to project management and software  development","collecting data method","answer4"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":2},{"question":" what\u2019s the Agile approach?","level":"difficult","answers":["anti-documentation","Scope can not vary","Development is non iterative","Requirements can not be changed"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":1},{"question":"what is the first thing to do for setting a requirement?","level":"easy","answers":["Present an initial plan","Identify the requirements","Characterization of risks","analyze the requirement"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":4},{"question":"Who are the System Requirement Review participants ?","level":"medium","answers":["survey documenter, Survey Director","survey presenter, survey documenter,Survey Director","Survey Director, survey presenter","Survey Director"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":2},{"question":"which of the following is a known testing method?","level":"easy","answers":["red box testing","green box testing","yellow box testing","white box testing"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":4},{"question":"which of the following is a known testing method\u201d?","level":"easy","answers":["black box testing","purple box testing","gray box testing","brown box testing"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":1},{"question":"what is software testing?","level":"medium","answers":["The process of analyzing a software item to detect the existing conditions","The process of analyzing a software item to detect the differences between         existing and required conditions ","The process of analyzing a software item only","The process of analyzing a software item to detect the required conditions"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":2},{"question":"The maintenance programmer must go through the phases of ?","level":"difficult","answers":["Requirements, Specifications, Design, Implementation and integration"," Design, Implementation and integration only","Design","Requirements and Specifications only "],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":1},{"question":"what\u2019s correct about software maintenance?","level":"medium","answers":["The term is mostly used for keeping custom software as it is","Maintenance does normally involve major changes to the system\u2019s architecture","Changes are implemented by only modifying existing components","Modifying a program after it has been put into use"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":4},{"question":"what are the Architecture patterns?","level":"medium","answers":["Model, View, Controller","Model, Controller"," Controller","Model"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":1},{"question":"What is Software Architecture?","level":"difficult","answers":["it\u2019s the set of principal design decisions about the system","it\u2019s the design of the software program","it\u2019s making fundamental structural choices that can\u2019t be changed once implemented","it\u2019s dealing with abstraction and style only"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":1},{"question":"what do we need for Review preparation?","level":"easy","answers":["Leader","participants","Leader and participants","only one participant "],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":3},{"question":"what are the different types of review?","level":"medium","answers":["Quality reviews,Inspections for defect removal","Reviews for progress assessment ","Quality reviews,Reviews for progress assessment, Inspections for defect removal","Reviews for progress assessment,Quality reviews "],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":3},{"question":"what is Blach-Box testing?","level":"difficult","answers":["testing method in which the internal structure/ design/ implementation of the item being tested is not known to the tester","testing method in which the internal structure/ design/ implementation of the item being tested is known to the tester","testing method in which the internal structure/ design/ implementation of the item being tested is known to the tester","testing method in which the internal structure/ design/ implementation of the item being tested is not known to the tester"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":1}]]}